const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What does the 'NaN' stand for in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "Not a Null"],
          ["B", "Not a Number"],
          ["C", "No Assignment"],
          ["D", "Null and Not Defined"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which operator is used for strict equality in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "=="],
          ["B", "==="],
          ["C", "!="],
          ["D", "!=="]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'return' statement in a function?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "To end the function execution"],
          ["B", "To return a value from the function"],
          ["C", "To declare a variable"],
          ["D", "To console log a message"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which function is used to convert a string to an integer in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "parseInt()"],
          ["B", "parseFloat()"],
          ["C", "toInteger()"],
          ["D", "convertToInt()"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A"
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "What does the 'typeof' operator return in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "The type of the variable"],
          ["B", "The value of the variable"],
          ["C", "The length of the variable"],
          ["D", "The index of the variable"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A"
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which event is triggered when a user clicks on an HTML element?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "onhover"],
          ["B", "onmove"],
          ["C", "onclick"],
          ["D", "ondrag"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "C"
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'try', 'catch', and 'finally' blocks in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "To create loops"],
          ["B", "To handle exceptions"],
          ["C", "To define functions"],
          ["D", "To declare variables"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'localStorage' object in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "To store data on the server"],
          ["B", "To store data on the client-side"],
          ["C", "To store session data"],
          ["D", "To store temporary data"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which method is used to join elements of an array into a string in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "concat()"],
          ["B", "merge()"],
          ["C", "join()"],
          ["D", "combine()"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "C"
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'fetch' API in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
          ["A", "To fetch data from a database"],
          ["B", "To fetch resources from the network"],
          ["C", "To fetch CSS styles"],
          ["D", "To fetch images"]
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B"
      },
]